Guide to the Biographical Information on Yale University Affiliated Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Biographical information on Yale University faculty, circa 1938-1990; Accession 1995-A-033
  - Morris, John, M.D. (Box 4, Folder 299)
  - Morris, Rev. Raymond (Box 4, Folder 300)
  - Morris, Sarah P. (Box 4, Folder 301)
  - Moulthrop, Stuart (Box 4, Folder 302)
  - Mueller, Otto-Werner (Box 4, Folder 303)
  - Murnaghan, Sheila (Box 4, Folder 304)
  - Nagler, Alois (Box 4, Folder 305)
  - Needham, Wesley E. (Box 4, Folder 306)
  - Newmark, Kevin (Box 4, Folder 307)
  - Nichols, Carol Wood (Box 4, Folder 308)
  - Nicoll, Francis (Box 4, Folder 309)
  - Nochlin, Linda (Box 4, Folder 310)
  - Northrop, Filmer S. C. (Box 4, Folder 311)
  - Nouvel, Claire (Box 4, Folder 312)
  - Olyan, Saul Mitchell (Box 4, Folder 313)
  - Orphanoudakis, Stelios C. (Box 4, Folder 314)
  - Osterweis, Rollin G. (Box 4, Folder 315)
  - Owen, Benton B. (Box 4, Folder 316)
  - Palade, George M.D. (Box 4, Folder 317)
  - Palmeri, Rosario, M.D. (Box 4, Folder 318)
  - Papermaster, David, M.D. (Box 4, Folder 319)
  - Parish, Howard (Box 4, Folder 320)
  - Partridge, Chester (Box 4, Folder 321)
  - Patterson, Andrew (Box 4, Folder 322)
  - Pauly, Edward W. (Box 4, Folder 323)
  - Peixoto, Maria Chaves (Box 4, Folder 324)
  - Perlis, Alan J. (Box 4, Folder 325)
  - Peters, William (Box 4, Folder 326)
  - Peterson, Stephen L. (Box 4, Folder 327)
  - Peyre, Henri (Box 4, Folder 328)
  - Pickford, Grace E. (Box 4, Folder 329)
  - Piedra, Jose (Box 4, Folder 330)
  - Plotke, David (Box 4, Folder 331)
  - Polan, Mary Lake (Box 4, Folder 332)
  - Polla, Dennis L. (Box 4, Folder 333)
  - Pope, Albert H. (Box 4, Folder 334)
  - Poulson, Donald F. (Box 4, Folder 335)
  - Powell, Walter W. (Box 4, Folder 336)
  - Price, Ken (Box 4, Folder 337)
  - Provence, Sally A. (Box 4, Folder 338)
  - Psacharopoulos, Nikos (Box 4, Folder 339)
  - Pulice, Maria Alicia (Box 4, Folder 340)
  - Purdy, Richard L. (Box 4, Folder 341)
  - Rado, Leslie (Box 5, Folder 342)
  - Rahder, Johannes (Box 5, Folder 343)
  - Ramicova, Dunya L. (Box 5, Folder 344)
  - Rasmussen, Howard, M.D. (Box 5, Folder 345)
  - Rasmussen, Jane S., M.D. (Box 5, Folder 346)
  - Redlich, Fredrick C. (Box 5, Folder 347)
  - Reed, Adolph, Jr. (Box 5, Folder 348)
  - Reid, Martine (Box 5, Folder 349)
  - Rescorla, Robert A. (Box 5, Folder 350)
  - Reynolds, Herbert, M.D. (Box 5, Folder 351)
  - Rhodes, Robin Francis (Box 5, Folder 352)
  - Rieder, Jonathan (Box 5, Folder 353)
  - Ringwald, John W. (Box 5, Folder 354)
  - Robertson, William (Box 5, Folder 355)
  - Robinson, Charles (Box 5, Folder 356)
  - Robinson, Thomas, M.D. (Box 5, Folder 357)
  - Robson, John E. (Box 5, Folder 358)
  - Rodriguez-Becchini, Hugo (Box 5, Folder 359)
  - Rolland, Peter G. (Box 5, Folder 360)
  - Romero, Mary (Box 5, Folder 361)
  - Rosenberg, Leon E. (Box 5, Folder 362)
  - Rosenberg, Marc, M.D. (Box 5, Folder 363)
  - Rosenberg, Mindy (Box 5, Folder 364)
  - Rossomando, Joseph (Box 5, Folder 365)
  - Rothlein, Joan E. (Box 5, Folder 366)
  - Roy, Charles E. (Box 5, Folder 367)
  - Rubin, Barnett R. (Box 5, Folder 368)
  - Ruszala, Jeanne A. (Box 5, Folder 369)
  - Ryan, Frank B. (Box 5, Folder 370)
  - Sah, Raaj Kumar (Box 5, Folder 371)
  - Samuel, Arthur G. (Box 5, Folder 372)
  - Savin, Gordan (Box 5, Folder 373)
  - Schaefer, H. Reiner (Box 5, Folder 374)
  - Schank, Roger C. (Box 5, Folder 375)
  - Schiff, Martin Jr., M.D. (Box 5, Folder 376)
  - Schreiber, Stuart L. (Box 5, Folder 377)
  - Schwartz, Gary E. (Box 5, Folder 378)
  - Schwartz, Solomon, M.D. (Box 5, Folder 379)
  - Sears, Paul B. (Box 5, Folder 380)
  - Sega., Erich (Box 5, Folder 381)
  - Senn, Milton, M.D. (Box 5, Folder 382)
  - Symour, charles (Box 5, Folder 383)
  - Shapiro, Matthew D. (Box 5, Folder 384)
  - Shapiro, Robert, M.D. (Box 5, Folder 385)
  - Shepard, Brooks, Jr. (Box 5, Folder 386)
  - Sherman, Nancy (Box 5, Folder 387)
  - Shibayama, Toshiko (Box 5, Folder 388)
  - Shivakumar, Balasubramanian (Box 5, Folder 389)
  - Simonds, Bruce (Box 5, Folder 390)
  - Singer, Lynn (Box 5, Folder 391)
  - Smith, Howard W. (Box 5, Folder 392)
  - Smith, Michael G. (Box 5, Folder 393)
  - Smith, Ora L.K. (Box 5, Folder 394)
  - Smith, Stephen J. (Box 5, Folder 395)
  - Snoke, Albert, M.D. (Box 5, Folder 396)
  - Soloway, Elliot M. (Box 5, Folder 397)
  - Spacks, Patricia M. (Box 5, Folder 398)
  - Spates, Thomas G. (Box 5, Folder 399)
  - Spadafora, David (Box 5, Folder 400)
  - Stacey, Robert C. (Box 5, Folder 401)
  - Stanfield, John Houston, II (Box 5, Folder 402)
  - Stenn, Kurt, M.D. (Box 5, Folder 403)
  - Stern, Blake G. (Box 5, Folder 404)
  - Stevens, Charles F. (Box 5, Folder 405)
  - Stevens, Jane R. (Box 5, Folder 406)
  - Stevenson, Bruce R. (Box 5, Folder 407)
  - Stoddard, Carlos F. (Box 5, Folder 408)
  - Strauss, John A. (Box 5, Folder 409)
  - Stroup, John (Box 5, Folder 410)
  - Strozer, Judith R. (Box 5, Folder 411)
  - Sussez, Ian (Box 5, Folder 412)
  - Swigar, Mary, M.D. (Box 5, Folder 413)
  - Talley, Sandra (Box 6, Folder 414)
  - Thompson, John D. (Box 6, Folder 415)
  - Thomson, Elizabeth (Box 6, Folder 416)
  - Thomson, Keith (Box 6, Folder 417)
  - Tinsley, Beatrice (Box 6, Folder 418)
  - Tischler, Gary L., M.D. (Box 6, Folder 419)
  - Tomita, Tsuneo (Box 6, Folder 420)
  - Tracy, Joseph S. (Box 6, Folder 421)
  - Triffin, Robert (Box 6, Folder 422)
  - Tsien, Billie (Box 6, Folder 423)
  - Tsien, Richard W. (Box 6, Folder 424)
  - Turnbull, Gordon (Box 6, Folder 425)
  - Tuteur, Franz B. (Box 6, Folder 426)
  - Underwood, Barbara (Box 6, Folder 427)
  - Ungerer, James C. (Box 6, Folder 428)
  - Uthoff, Michael (Box 6, Folder 429)
  - Van Cleve, Susan N. (Box 6, Folder 430)
  - Van Den Toorn, Pieter (Box 6, Folder 431)
  - Van Der Heyden, Ludo (Box 6, Folder 432)
  - Vine, Brent (Box 6, Folder 433)
  - Viseltear, Arthur J. (Box 6, Folder 434)
  - Von Schlegell, David (Box 6, Folder 435)
  - Varga, Janos M. (Box 6, Folder 436)
  - Van Roosmalen, Onno S. (Box 6, Folder 437)
  - Waldvogel, Michael (Box 6, Folder 438)
  - Walters, Jo Ann (Box 6, Folder 439)
  - Walsh, James F., III (Box 6, Folder 440)
  - Warnke, Georgia C. (Box 6, Folder 441)
  - Warren, Robert Penn (Box 6, Folder 442)
  - Waterman, John A. (Box 6, Folder 443)
  - Watson, Donald R. (Box 6, Folder 444)
  - Weaver, Howard S. (Box 6, Folder 445)
  - Weinman, David, II (Box 6, Folder 446)
  - Weir, David R. (Box 6, Folder 447)
  - Weiss, Paul (Box 6, Folder 448)
  - Weissman, Myrna (Box 6, Folder 449)
  - Whalley, John (Box 6, Folder 450)
  - Wheelwright, Carolyn (Box 6, Folder 451)
  - White, George C. (Box 6, Folder 452)
  - Whitman, Loring, M.D. (Box 6, Folder 453)
  - Whitman, Martin J. (Box 6, Folder 454)
  - Wicke, Jennifer A. (Box 6, Folder 455)
  - Williams, David R. (Box 6, Folder 456)
  - Wilkinson, John A. (Box 6, Folder 457)
  - Williamson, Oliver E. (Box 6, Folder 458)
  - Winter, Sidney G. (Box 6, Folder 459)
  - Wofford, Susanne L. (Box 6, Folder 460)
  - Woodward, Susan (Box 6, Folder 461)
  - Wolin, Elliott J. (Box 6, Folder 462)
  - Wong, Andrew S., M.D. (Box 6, Folder 463)
  - Wong, Shek-Fu (Box 6, Folder 464)
  - Woods, Alan R. (Box 6, Folder 465)
  - Wright, Nancy E. (Box 6, Folder 466)
  - Zavala, Maria Elena (Box 6, Folder 467)
  - Zelenak, Michael (Box 6, Folder 468)
- Material collected on George H.W. Bush, 1948-1991; Accession 1995-A-082
  Ope for research.
  - Accelerator dedication, 1987 August (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Articles, various (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Biographies, 1974-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3 - 4)
  - Commencement, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon Fraternity, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Family, 1917-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kennebunkport, Maine (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Looking Forward, an Autobiography, photocopies from book, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Meeting with Yale president Benno Schmidt, 1988 December (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Photographs
    - Baseball team, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Baseball uniform, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Various, 1970s-1980s (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Yale class book, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Presidential inauguration, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Vice President, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - World War II (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Yale career (including baseball statistics) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "The Way We Were in Poppy's Day," Yale Alumni Magazine, 1989 February (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Yale Class of 1948, 40th Anniversary year book, clippings and photographs, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Yale Political Union press kit, 1980 February 24 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Deceased faculty files, circa 1950s-2009; Accession 2010-A-009
  The materials consist of obituaries, news clippings, vitae, and press releases documenting deceased Yale faculty.
  - Ake, Claude (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ames, Louise Bates (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Apfel, Robert (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Arnstein, Robert, MD (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Arrom, Jose (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Beringer, E. Robert (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Black, Charles L. (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - Blair, Edwin Foster (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Blassingame, John W. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bockelman, Charles k. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Boell, Edgar J. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Boorsch, Jean (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Brooks, Cleanth (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Broude, Henry W. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Brown, Ralph S., Jr. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cahow, Clarence E. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Casals-Ariet, Jordi, MD (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Chase, Alice Elizabeth (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Chupka, William A. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Cohen, Donald Jay, MD (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Crowder, Robert G. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Crowley, James B. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Darling, George B. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Daszuta, Wesley, Sr. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - De Man, Paul (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Donaldson, Robert, MD (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Dunham, Clarence W. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Evans, Alfred S., MD (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Fei, John C. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Feinstein, Alvan, MD (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Fesler, James W. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Forge, Andrew (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Frankel, Hans H. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - French, Richard (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Friedman, Erick (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Gillis, Charles N. (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Goodyer, Allan, MD (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Goold, George P. (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Gould, Thomas Fauss (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Greene, Thomas (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Griswold, Mary (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Guicharnaud, Jacques (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Hamburger, Joseph (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - HaIl, John Whitney (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Hanson, Anne Coffin (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Henderson, Virginia (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Hersey, John (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Hexter, Jack H. (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Holmer, Paul L. (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Horstmann, Dorothy, MD (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Hramov, Konstantin (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Hutchinson, Franklin (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Jackson, Stanley W., MD (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Janeway, Charles (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Johnson, Rev. Robert C. (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Jordan, Richard G. (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Kaplow, Leonard S., MD (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Kubler, George A. (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Lang, Serge (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Levinson, Daniel J. (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Lewis, Richard W.B. (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Lewis, Robert (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Liebert, Herman W. (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Lindskog, Gustaf, MD (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Mack, Maynard (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Margenau, Henry (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Marshall, Burke (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Martz, Louis (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - May, George (Box 2, Folder 70-71)
  - McCarthy, Mary A. (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Meigs, J. Wister, MD (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Metlitzki, Dorothee (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Miller, John Perry (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Miller, Neal E. (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Miller, Rev. Randolph C. (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Miller, Richard S. (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Miller, Spencer F. (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Miskimin, Harry A. (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Moore, James W. (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Myers, Jerome K. (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Noss, Luther (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Nouwen, Rev. Henri (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Ostrom, John (Box 3, Folder 85-86)
  - Poirion, Daniel (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Rand, Paul (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Redlich, Fredrick C., MD (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Richards, Lloyd (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Rickart, Charles (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Robley, Grant (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Rodgers, John (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Rouse, Irving (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Rudin, Harry, Sr. (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Rudolph, Paul (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Ruggles, Richard (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Saltzman, Barry (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Schor, Naomi (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Schrader, George A. (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Scott, Dennis (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Sewall, Richard B. (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Sigler, Paul (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Smith, John E. (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Solnit, Albert, MD (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Sullivan, Kathleen A. (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Thompson, Bradbury (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Turner, Henry A., Jr. (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Vincent-Daviss, Diana (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Voigt, Garth K. (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Walker, Charles A. (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Wellek, Rene (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Winks, Robin W. (Box 4, Folder 113-114)
  - Woodward, C. Vann (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Wu, King-Lui (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Zallinger, Rudolph F. (Box 5, Folder 118)
- Deceased faculty files, 1858, 1962, 1984, 1991-2009; Accession 2011-A-023
  - Allen, Greer, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Beckett, Ronald S., 2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bliss, William, Rev., 2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Boswell, John E., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bowman, Ward S., Jr., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Brass, Lawrence, M.D., 2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Buffum, Imbrie, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Byck, Robert, M.D., 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Child, Irvin L., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Childs, Brevard S., 2007 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Christian, William, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cohen, Melvin J., 1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correa, Gustavo, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Culler, Dwight A., 2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cunningham, W. Jack, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Davenny, Ward, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - DeCarvalho, Eleazar, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - DeLoache, Benjamin, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Dittes, James E., 2009 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Dahl, Nils Alstrup, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - D'Esopo, Nicholas, M.D., 2008 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dock, Donald S., M.D., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Doob, Leonard, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Douglas, William, M.D., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Druckman, Jacob, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Dyen, Isadore, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Ecklund, John E., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Edelson, Marshall, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Emerson, Thomas, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Erlich, Victor, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Feidelson, Charles, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Feit, Walter, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Fleck, Stephen, M.D., 2002 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Fryer, Gary, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Gallup, Donald, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Galston, Arthur W., 2008 (Box 1, Folder 36-37)
  - Garfinkel, Boris, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Glenn, William W. L., 2003 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Goldman-Rakic, Patricia, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Granger, Richard H., 2001 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Greenberg, Jack, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Greene, Nicholas, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Heath, Fenno F., 2008 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Hebert, Steven C., M.D., 2008 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Herington, C. John, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Hersey, George L., 2007 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Hicks,Robert, Rev., 2008 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Hoffer, Paul B., M.D., 2006 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Hoffleit, Dorrit, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Horvath, Csaba, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Howe, Kathleen, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Hsiung, Gueh-Djen, M.D., 2006 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Huang, Parker, P., 2008 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Hubley, Faith, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Hunter, George K., 2008 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Jacobson, Nathan, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Katz, Jay, M.D., 2008 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Kavanagh, Aidan, Rev., 2006 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Kezerian, Stephen, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Kirkpatrick, John, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Kleeman, James A., M.D., 2007 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Klein, Martin J., 2009 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Körner, Stephan, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Lane, Cecil T., 1991 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Lee, Richard C., 2003 (Box 2, Folder 66-68)
  - Leonard, Martha, M.D., 2006 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Lerner, Aaron, M.D., 2007 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Lewis, Melvin, M.D., 2007 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Liberman, Alvin M., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Lidz, Theodore, M.D., 2001 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Lipson, Leon, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Lounsbury, Floyd, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Lyons, Philip A., 2006 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Macnab, Robert M., 2003 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Mahl, George F., M.D., 2006 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Mastrangelo, Jerry, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - McClellan, Edwin, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - McDougal, Myres S., 1998 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - McGuire, William J., 2007 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - McKhan, Charles F., M.D., 2005 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Middleton, Jon F., 2009 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Milgram, Stanley, M.D., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Millard, Peter, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Miller, Joseph A., 1998 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Montias, John A., 2005 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Mood, Eric W., 2004 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Napier, Davie, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Natanson, Maurice, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Naylor, Audrey, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Novick, Alvin, M.D., 2005 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Noyce, Gaylord, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - O'Hearn, Charles M., 2001 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Olmsted, Denison, 1859 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Onat, Emin Turan, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Palisca, Claude V., 2001 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Palmer, Robert R., 2002 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Parker, William N., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Pepine, Arthur, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Peterdi, Gabor R., 2001 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Pierson, George W., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Pope, Marvin H., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Pope, John C., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Reifsnyder, William, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Reiser, Morton F., M.D., 2007 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Reiss, Albert J., Jr., 2006 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Remington, Charles, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 109-110)
  - Reynolds, Lloyd G., 2005 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Reynolds, Mary, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Richards, Frederick M., 2009 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Ritchie, Murdock, M.D., 2008 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Ross, Arthur M., 2004 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Rosenthal, Franz, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Roseman, Ronald, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Rostow, Eugene V., 2002 (Box 3, Folder 118-120)
  - Russell, Lyent W., 1998 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Samuel, Harold E., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Savage, I. Richard, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Schmidt, Michael, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Shaumyan, Sebastian, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Shope, Robert, M.D., 2004 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Sibley, Charles G., 1998 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Smith, David Martyn, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Spiegel, Herman D.J., 2008 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Sturtevant, Julian, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Thompson, Leonard M., 2004 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Triffin, Robert, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Trinkaus, John P., 2003 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Waage, Karl M., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Waith, Eugene M., 2007 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Wegener, Peter P., 2008 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Wells, Rulon Seumour, III, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Westerfield, Bradford H., 2008 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Wittink, Dick R., 2005 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Worrell, Albert C., 2000 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Wynne, Marjorie, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 141)